PERSONAL INFORMATION

Name: MOHAMMAD REZZA DANIAL BIN MD AMIR

Age: 22

Date of Birth: 14 MAY 1995

Address: 11 JALAN PEGAGA U12/7, DESA ALAM SEKSYEN 7,

40170 SHAH ALAM, SELANGOR

Marital Status: Single

Mobile: 017 482 5310

Email: rezzadanialcs@gmail.com

Internship Period: 19 February 2018 – 6 July 2018



PROFILE

I am a versatile young professional intending to continue my career as Network Engineer. I think in term of results and objectives, I am workaholic, and I work with decisiveness and full with passion. I have a proactive attitude and find positive ways to stimulate and engage with any group of community. Even though I am just 22 years old, I have a lot of professional experience in many field. I was trained to be a great leader with strong physical and mental readiness. In term of social life, I am a friendly person and able to cope with every kind of social group.

EDUCATION

2016 – Present

Bachelor Degree in Netcentric Computing

MARA Technology University, Shah Alam



- Major in Web Development and Computer Networking
- Relevant Courses: Network Administration, CCNA, Linux,
 Digital Electronics
- Final Year Project: Unifying Crowdsourcing Platform using Ruby on Rails
- Current CGPA: 3.21

2013 - 2015

Diploma in Computer Science

MARA Technology University, Perlis



- Learnt general and fundamentals of all computer science branches
- Relevant Courses: Object Oriented Programming,
 Multimedia, Data Communication,
 Operating System

CGPA: 3.06

2011 - 2012

Sijil Pelajaran Malaysia (SPM)



Sekolah Menengah Sains Tun Syed Sheh Shahabudin

- Science Stream and ICT Student
- SPM: 5A, 3B, 2C

TECHNICAL CERTIFICATION AND COURSES

25 November 2017 Server Infrastructure Penetration Testing



Training.my and Serai Solution

Technical Course about Penetration Testing

- Hands on training using Hacking Tools like Nmap, Metasploit, Nessus, BurpSuite and Kali Linux
- Trainer: Shamriman Samsudin
 - **GIAC Penetration Tester (GPEN)**

7 – 8 October 2017 ISACA Cybersecurity Nexus Fundamentals



Malaysia Digital Economy Corporation

- **Bootcamp course about Cybersecurity world**
- Learn about Information System Security

October 2015

Certified Internet Protocol Associate Course by Orbitage



MARA Technology University, Pulau Pinang

- Technical Certification in Computer Networking
- Successfully undergo the course and pass the exam
- Exam Result: 84 %

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

May 2016 – Present

Trainer under Malaysia Digital Economy Cooperation (MDEC)

Pusat eRezeki Shah Alam, Seksyen 16, Shah Alam



- Consult and train a local citizen about government digital economy programme
- **Facilitate** them to earn side income from doing online jobs.

JULY 2015

Production Operators at Western Digital

Western Digital (Media), Penang



- Six months experience cumulative in manufacturing industrial as production operator
- manufacturing computer hard disk storage.

June - October 2015

Chief Commander for Kesatria Uniform Society

MARA Technology University, Perlis



- **Responsible in relationship** between society with 150 members and university's student affair.
- Plan and manage co-curriculum course for approximately 2000 students each semester.
- Organize and manage activities for society members.

June 2014 – October 2015

Instructor Assistant for Students Affair

MARA Technology University, Perlis



- Assist the Instructor during Co-Curriculum activities such as rope climbing, abseiling, marching, first aid course.
- Manage the student's files and attendance.

HIGHLIGHTS OF EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES & ACHIEVEMENTS

25 October 2017	Dean Award for Semester 5
4 – 9 August 2017	Mount Tahan Hiking Expedition
1 – 2 September 2016	Mount Kinabalu Hiking Expedition
10 – 28 May 2015	Volunteer Programme at Cambodia
9 – 11 January 2015	Flood Disaster Volunteer at Kuala Krai, Kelantan
30 November 2013	Art Life Islam Festival Short Film Competition (Second Runner Up)
25 October –	Commander Kesatria Intensive Training
25 October – 8 November 2013	Commander Kesatria Intensive Training
	Commander Kesatria Intensive Training Rector Cup Debating Competition (Second Runner Up)
8 November 2013	
8 November 2013 23 September 2013	Rector Cup Debating Competition (Second Runner Up)
8 November 2013 23 September 2013	Rector Cup Debating Competition (<i>Second Runner Up</i>) Competitive Programming and Multimedia Competition

LANGUAGE & SKILLS

Language:

- Bahasa Malaysia
 - Written: Excellent
 - Spoken: Excellent
 - Reading: Excellent
- English
 - Written: Excellent
 - Spoken: Excellent
 - o **Reading:** Excellent

Technical Skills:

- Network Design
 - o IP Addressing, Logical Design, Network Administration
- Penetration Testing
 - o Nmap, UNIX, Wireshark, Metasploit, Nessus
- Mobile/Web Application Development
 - o iOS, Ruby On Rails, PHP Laravel, HTML, Bootstrap, JAVA
- Photo and Video Editing
 - o Adobe Creative Suite, Final Cut Pro X
- IT Helpdesk

OS Configuration, Hardware Setup

REFERENCES

1) Hjh. Khalidah Binti Abdul Karim

- Chairman of Pusat eRezeki Shah Alam
- Former Chief Financial Officer at Bank Negara Malaysia
- Contact Number: 012 218 6655

2) Mohd Najib Bin Mohd Redzuan

- Head Officer of Co-Curriculum Unit at UiTM Perlis
- Contact Number: 016 415 2625

3) Dr Shahniza Binti Kamal Bashah

- Final Year Project Supervisor and Lecturer
- Contact Number: 019 212 2622